#### Contact

7024279104 (Mobile) charissa316@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/charissadavis-97562596 (LinkedIn) gmail.com (Personal) orovalleyhospital.com (Company)

### Top Skills

Healthcare Healthcare Management Nursing

# **Charissa Davis**

Travel Psychiatric Nurse at Aya Healthcare

Phoenix, Arizona Area

## Summary

Charissa is an accomplished health care leader with more than 20 years of progressively

care for the elderly. She has demonstrated skills in planning and the successful execution of complex health care projects; has well developed written and verbal communication skills. Considered energetic, fair, persistent and approachable, with the ability to motivate and maximize team and staff performance. Has experience in for profit and not for profit organizations. Charissa has a great commitment to Nursing and its future and holds her staff to a high degree of professional accountability. She is frequently seen working side by side with her staff in times of crisis and daily unit operations. As a motivated nursing leader with unlimited energy, she is an excellent selection in assisting an organization in achieving its objectives.

# Experience

Aya Healthcare
Travel Psychiatric Nurse
February 2020 - Present (5 months)
Escondido, California, United States

Stability Healthcare RN-BC, MSL Travel RN July 2019 - February 2020 (8 months) Los Angeles, California

Escondido CA, Palomar Hospital

Supplemental Health Care RN-BC,MSL September 2016 - February 2020 (3 years 6 months) Long Beach, California

Travel Rn Psychiatric Nurse

Oro Valley Hospital
Director Of Nursing
February 2017 - June 2019 (2 years 5 months)
Oro Valley Az

Nursing Director of the Senior Behavioral Health Unit "Choices"

# Oasis Behavioral Health Hospital CNO

September 2014 - September 2016 (2 years 1 month)

Chandler, Arizona

Haven Behavioral Healthcare
Director of Nursing, Senior Leader
November 2012 - September 2014 (1 year 11 months)

Carondelet Health Network St. Mary's July 2005 - 2009 (4 years)

ABCM Corporation Corporate Quality Assurance Nurse 1997 - 2003 (6 years)

# Education

### Bellevue University

Masters in Leadership, Health/Health Care Administration/ Management · (2003 - 2004)

### Bellevue University

Healthcare Management, Health/Health Care Administration/ Management · (1998 - 2000)

### St Luke's College

Dipolma, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1990 - 1993)